A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1936
  - Europe, 1936; 1936/700
    - Europe - (R-T), 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1042)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/700.S
      - Europe, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1042)
  - Austria, 1936; 1936/705
    - Austria, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/705.E
      - Austria, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
    - Austria - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/705.S
      - Austria, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
  - Belgium, 1936; 1936/707
    - Belgium, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
  - Yugoslavia, 1936; 1936/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
  - Bulgaria, 1936; 1936/711
    - Bulgaria, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1043)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1936; 1936/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1044)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1044)
  - Denmark, 1936; 1936/713
    - Denmark, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1044)
    - Denmark - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/713.S
      - Denmark, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1044)
  - Germany, 1936; 1936/717
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - List, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1045)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - Academic Assistance Council - (Murrow Committee), 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1046)
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Murrow Committee), 1936 (Box 140, Folder 1047)
    - Germany - (A-L), 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1048)
    - Germany - (M-Z), 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1049)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/717.E
      - Germany, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1050)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/717.S
      - Germany, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1050)
  - Hungary, 1936; 1936/750
    - Hungary, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1050)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/750.E
      - Hungary, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1050)
    - Hungary - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/750.S
      - Hungary, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1050)
  - Italy, 1936; 1936/751
    - Italy, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/751.E
      - Italy, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/751.S
      - Italy, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
  - Norway, 1936; 1936/767
    - Norway, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/767.E
      - Norway, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
  - Romania, 1936; 1936/783
    - Romania, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
  - USSR, 1936; 1936/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
    - GUNN Gunn, Selskar M. "Notes and Comments on a trip to the USSR", 1936 (Box 559, Folder 3798)
    - USSR - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/785.E
      - U.S.S.R., 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1051)
  - Finland, 1936; 1936/787
    - Finland, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
    - Finland - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/787.S
      - Finland, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
  - Poland, 1936; 1936/789
    - Poland, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/789.E
      - Poland, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
  - Sweden, 1936; 1936/800
    - Sweden, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/800.E
      - Sweden, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1936; 1936/800.S
      - Sweden, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
  - Switzerland, 1936; 1936/803
    - Switzerland, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
  - Turkey, 1936; 1936/805
    - Turkey, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1936; 1936/805.E
      - Turkey, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1052)
  - Cyprus, 1936; 1936/809
    - Cypru - (A-S) - Stratman-Thomas, W. K., 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1053)
    - Cyprus - Stratman-Thomas, W. K., 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1054)
- General Correspondence, 1937
  - International, 1937; 1937/100
    - (A-G), 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1055)
    - (H-I), 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1056)
    - (J-L), 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1057)
    - (M-S), 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1058)
    - (S-Z), 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1059)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/100.A
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1060)
    - International - Nursing, 1937; 1937/100.C
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1060)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1937; 1937/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1060)
    - International - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/100.R
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1060)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/100.S
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1060)
  - United States, 1937; 1937/200
    - United States - (A-Am), 1937 (Box 142, Folder 1061)
    - United States - (Am-Ar), 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1062)
    - United States - (Ar-Bl), 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1063)
    - United States - (Co-Ch), 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1064)
    - United States - (Ci-Co), 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1065)
    - United States - Cook, Thomas and Son, 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1066)
    - United States - (Co-E), 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1067)
    - United States - (F-Ge), 1937 (Box 143, Folder 1068)
    - United States - (Ge-Gz), 1937 (Box 144, Folder 1069)
    - United States - (H-K), 1937 (Box 144, Folder 1070)
    - United States - (L-Ma), 1937 (Box 144, Folder 1071)
    - United States - (Ma-Mo), 1937 (Box 144, Folder 1072)
    - United States - (Mu-Na), 1937 (Box 144, Folder 1073)
    - United States - (Na-Ne), 1937 (Box 144, Folder 1074)
    - United States - Nemours Foundation for Crippled Children, 1937 (Box 145, Folder 1075)
    - United States - (Ne-Pa), 1937 (Box 145, Folder 1076)
    - United States - (Pe-Pz), 1937 (Box 145, Folder 1077)
    - United States - (Q-Sp), 1937 (Box 145, Folder 1078)
    - United States - (Sr-T), 1937 (Box 145, Folder 1079)
    - United States - (United States: Africulture - Public Health Service), 1937 (Box 145, Folder 1080)
    - United States - (U.S. Senate - Z), 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1081)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/200.A
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1082)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1937; 1937/200.D
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1082)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/200.E
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1082)
      - United States - (H-U), 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1083)
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1084)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/200.R
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1084)
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1085)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/200.S
      - United States, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1085)
      - United States - Social Science Research Council, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1086)
  - Alabama, 1937; 1937/201
    - Alabama, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
  - Arizona, 1937; 1937/203
    - Arizona, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
  - Arkansas, 1937; 1937/204
    - Arkansas, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
  - California, 1937; 1937/205
    - California, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
    - California - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/205.A
      - California, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/205.S
      - California, 1937 (Box 146, Folder 1087)
  - Colorado, 1937; 1937/207
    - Colorado, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
    - Colorado - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/207.R
      - Colorado, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
  - Connecticut, 1937; 1937/208
    - Connecticut, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
  - Florida, 1937; 1937/211
    - Florida, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
  - Georgia, 1937; 1937/212
    - Georgia, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1088)
  - Idaho, 1937; 1937/215
    - Idaho, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
  - Illinois, 1937; 1937/216
    - Illinois, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
  - Indiana, 1937; 1937/217
    - Indiana - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/217.R
      - Indiana, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
  - Kansas, 1937; 1937/219
  - Kentucky, 1937; 1937/220
    - Kentucky, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
  - Louisiana, 1937; 1937/221
    - Louisiana - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/221.S
      - Louisiana, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
  - Maine, 1937; 1937/222
    - Maine, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1089)
  - Minnesota, 1937; 1937/226
    - Minnesota, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - Mississippi, 1937; 1937/227
    - Mississippi, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
    - Mississippi - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/227.S
      - Mississippi, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - Missouri, 1937; 1937/228
    - Missouri, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
    - Missouri - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/228.E
      - Missouri, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - Montana, 1937; 1937/229
    - Montana, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - Nebraska, 1937; 1937/230
    - Nebraska, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - New Hampshire, 1937; 1937/232
    - New Hampshire, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - New Jersey, 1937; 1937/233
    - New Jersey, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1090)
  - New Mexico, 1937; 1937/234
    - New Mexico, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1091)
  - North Carolina, 1937; 1937/236
    - North Carolina, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1091)
    - North Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/236.E
      - North Carolina, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1091)
  - North Dakota, 1937; 1937/237
    - North Dakota, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1091)
    - North Dakota - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/237.R
      - North Dakota, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1091)
  - Ohio, 1937; 1937/238
    - Ohio, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
  - Oregon, 1937; 1937/240
    - Oregon, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
  - Pennsylvania, 1937; 1937/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
    - Pennsylvania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1937; 1937/241.D
      - Pennsylvania, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
  - Rhode Island, 1937; 1937/244
    - Rhode Island, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
  - South Carolina, 1937; 1937/246
    - South Carolina, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
    - South Carolina - Yellow Fever, 1937; 1937/246.O
      - South Carolina, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
  - South Dakota, 1937; 1937/247
    - South Dakota, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1092)
  - Tennessee, 1937; 1937/248
    - Tennessee, 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1093)
  - Utah, 1937; 1937/250
    - Utah, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1094)
  - Virginia, 1937; 1937/252
    - Virginia, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1095)
  - Washington, 1937; 1937/253
    - Washington, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1095)
  - West Virginia, 1937; 1937/254
    - West Virginia, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1096)
  - Wisconsin, 1937; 1937/255
    - Wisconsin, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1096)
  - Wyoming, 1937; 1937/256
    - Wyoming, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1096)
  - Virgin Islands, 1937; 1937/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1096)
  - South America, 1937; 1937/300
    - South America, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/300.S
      - South America, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
  - Argentina, 1937; 1937/301
    - Argentina, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
    - Argentina - Yellow Fever, 1937; 1937/301.O
      - Argentina, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
  - Bolivia, 1937; 1937/303
    - Bolivia, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
  - Chile, 1937; 1937/309
    - Chile, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/309.E
      - Chile, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
  - Colombia, 1937; 1937/311
    - Colombia, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1097)
  - Costa Rica, 1937; 1937/313
    - Costa Rica, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1098)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/313.E
      - Costa Rica, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1098)
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Education, 1937; 1937/313.L
      - Costa Rica, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1098)
  - Cuba, 1937; 1937/315
    - Cuba, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1098)
    - Cuba, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1099)
  - Ecuador, 1937; 1937/317
    - Ecuador, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1099)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/317.E
      - Ecuador, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1099)
  - Guatemala, 1937; 1937/319
    - Guatemala, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1099)
  - Mexico, 1937; 1937/323
    - Mexico, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1100)
    - Mexico - Nursing, 1937; 1937/323.C
      - Mexico, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1100)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/323.E
      - Mexico, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1100)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/323.S
      - Mexico, 1937 (Box 148, Folder 1100)
  - Nicaragua, 1937; 1937/325
    - Nicaragua, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1101)
    - Nicaragua - Malaria, 1937; 1937/325.I
      - Nicaragua, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1101)
  - Panama, 1937; 1937/327
    - Panama, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1101)
    - Panama - Nursing, 1937; 1937/327.C
      - Panama, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/327.E
      - Panama, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
  - Paraguay, 1937; 1937/329
    - Paraguay, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
    - Paraguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/329.E
      - Paraguay, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
  - Peru, 1937; 1937/331
    - Peru, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
  - El Salvador, 1937; 1937/333
    - El Salvador, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
    - El Salvador - Public Health Education, 1937; 1937/333.L
      - El Salvador, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
  - Dominican Republic, 1937; 1937/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1102)
  - Venezuela, 1937; 1937/339
    - Venezuela, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1103)
    - Venezuela - Health, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1104)
    - Venezuela - Health - Health Program, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1105)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1105)
  - Great Britain, 1937; 1937/400
    - Great Britain, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1106)
  - England, 1937; 1937/401
    - England - (A-P), 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1106)
    - England - (P-Z), 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1107)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/401.A
      - England, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1107)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1937; 1937/401.D
      - England, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1107)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/401.E
      - England, 1937 (Box 149, Folder 1107)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/401.S
      - England, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1108)
  - Wales, 1937; 1937/407
    - Wales, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1108)
  - Australia, 1937; 1937/410
    - Australia, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
    - Australia - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/410.S
      - Australia, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
  - New Zealand, 1937; 1937/418
    - New Zealand, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
  - Fiji, 1937; 1937/419
    - Fiji, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
    - Fiji - Nursing, 1937; 1937/419.C
      - Fiji, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
    - Fiji - Public Health Demonstrations, 1937; 1937/419.J
      - Fiji, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
  - Caribbean Region, 1937; 1937/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1109)
  - Belize, 1937; 1937/425
    - British Honduras, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1110)
  - Canada, 1937; 1937/427
    - Canada, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1110)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/427.A
      - Canada, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1110)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1937; 1937/427.D
      - Canada, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1110)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/427.E
      - Canada, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1110)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/427.R
      - Canada, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1111)
  - British East Indies, 1937; 1937/431
    - British East Indies, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1111)
  - Jamaica, 1937; 1937/437
    - Jamaica, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1111)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1111)
    - Jamaica - Yaws, 1937; 1937/437.U
      - Jamaica, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1111)
  - India, 1937; 1937/464
    - India - Administration, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1112)
    - India - (A-Z), 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1113)
    - JAC-1 Jacocks, W. P. "Touring Notes, 1936-1937" (Box 559, Folder 3799)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/464.A
      - India, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1113)
    - India - Nursing, 1937; 1937/464.C
      - India, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1113)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/464.E
      - India, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1113)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1937; 1937/464.L
      - India, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1113)
    - India - Mysore, 1937; 1937/464.1
      - India - (Mysore), 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
    - India - Travancore, 1937; 1937/464.5
      - India - (Travancore), 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
  - Africa, 1937; 1937/475
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/475.S
      - Africa, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/475.S
      - Africa, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
  - Nyasaland, 1937; 1937/482
    - Nyasaland, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
  - North Africa Region, 1937; 1937/485
    - Egypt, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
  - South Africa, 1937; 1937/487
    - South Africa, 1937 (Box 150, Folder 1114)
  - France, 1937; 1937/500
    - France, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1115)
    - France - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1937; 1937/500.D
      - France, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1116)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/500.E
      - France, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1116)
  - New Hebrides, 1937; 1937/536
    - New Hebrides, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1116)
  - Tunis, 1937; 1937/539
    - Tunis, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1116)
  - China, 1937; 1937/601
    - China - Administration, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1116)
    - China - (C-M), 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1117)
    - China - Peking Union Medical College, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1118)
    - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1119)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/601.A
      - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1119)
    - China - Nursing, 1937; 1937/601.C
      - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1119)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/601.E
      - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1120)
    - China - Public Health Demonstrations, 1937; 1937/601.J
      - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1120)
    - China - Public Health Education, 1937; 1937/601.L
      - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1120)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/601.R
      - China, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1120)
  - Japan, 1937; 1937/609
    - Japan, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1121)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/609.E
      - Japan, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1121)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1937; 1937/609.R
      - Japan, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1121)
  - Thailand, 1937; 1937/617
    - Thailand, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1121)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/617.E
      - Thailand, 1937 (Box 151, Folder 1121)
  - Holland, 1937; 1937/650
    - Netherlands, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1122)
  - Dutch Guiana, 1937; 1937/659
    - Dutch Guiana - Yellow Fever, 1937; 1937/659.O
      - Dutch Guiana, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1122)
  - Europe, 1937; 1937/700
    - Europe, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1122)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1937; 1937/700.A
      - Europe, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1122)
  - Albania, 1937; 1937/704
    - Albania, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1123)
    - Albania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/704.E
      - Albania, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1123)
  - Austria, 1937; 1937/705
    - Austria, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1123)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/705.E
      - Austria, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1123)
    - Austria - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/705.S
      - Austria, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1123)
  - Belgium, 1937; 1937/707
    - Belgium, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/707.E
      - Belgium, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
  - Belgian Congo (Zaire), 1937; 1937/709
    - Belgian Congo (Zaire), 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
  - Yugoslavia, 1937; 1937/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
  - Bulgaria, 1937; 1937/711
    - Bulgaria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/711.E
      - Bulgaria, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
    - Bulgaria - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/711.S
      - Bulgaria, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1937; 1937/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
  - Denmark, 1937; 1937/713
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/713.E
      - Denmark, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
    - Denmark - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/713.S
      - Denmark, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1124)
  - Germany, 1937; 1937/717
    - Germany - Exiled Scholars - (Baehr and Murrow Committee), 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1125)
    - Germany - (A-N), 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1126)
    - Germany - (N-Z), 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1127)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1937; 1937/717.D
      - Germany, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1128)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/717.E
      - Germany, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1128)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/717.S
      - Germany, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1128)
  - Hungary, 1937; 1937/750
    - Hungary, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1128)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/750.E
      - Hungary, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1128)
    - Hungary - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/750.S
      - Hungary, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 1128)
  - Italy, 1937; 1937/751
    - Italy, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/751.E
      - Italy, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
  - Norway, 1937; 1937/767
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/767.E
      - Norway, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
  - Portugal, 1937; 1937/773
    - Portugal, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
  - Romania, 1937; 1937/783
    - Romania, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
    - Romania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/783.E
      - Romania, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
  - USSR, 1937; 1937/785
    - U.S.S.R., 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
    - USSR - Social Sciences, 1937; 1937/785.S
      - U.S.S.R., 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1129)
  - Finland, 1937; 1937/787
    - Finland, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1130)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/787.E
      - Finland, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1130)
  - Lithuania, 1937; 1937/788
    - Lithuania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/788.E
      - Lithuania, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1130)
  - Poland, 1937; 1937/789
    - Poland, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1130)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1937; 1937/789.E
      - Poland, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 1130)
  - Sweden, 1937; 1937/800